When the questions are dangerous, the answers can be deadly.
Q & A is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Sidney Lumet.
A young district attorney seeking to prove a case against a corrupt police detective
encounters a former lover and her new protector, a crime boss who refuses to help him.
Mike Brennan, played by Nick Nolte.
Al Reilly, played by Timothy Hutton.
Bobby Texador, played by Armand Assante.
Kevin Quinn, played by Patrick O'Neal.
Leo Bloomenfeld, played by Lee Richardson.
Luis Valentin, played by Luis Guzmán.
Q & A is a 1990 American crime drama film written and directed by Sidney Lumet,
based on a novel by New York State Supreme Court judge Edwin Torres.
It stars Nick Nolte, Timothy Hutton, Armand Assante
and Lumet's daughter, Jenny Lumet.
The film explores themes of new york city, police brutality, based
on novel or book, crime boss, police corruption.
The tone is dark and intense.